talizma.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy – TALIZMA

We at Talizma, respect your privacy and are committed to protecting the information provided by you on this website.

We collect your email address to send you newsletter, new arrivals, updates & promotions of our alliance partners from our website from which you can choose to unsubscribe anytime.

Our website may contain links to other websites – usually giving credit to a particular piece of information . How the linked website collects your information is something we have no control over. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**The Information We Collect**

At some Talizma Sites, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information (such as your full name or email address) in order to participate in various activities, posting messages in our forums or in the video comments section, entering contests or sweepstakes, taking advantage of promotions, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. If accessing a Site from a mobile device, you may be asked to share your geo-location information if required, and identifiers designed to enable advertising on your device may be used by us or our service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and partners. You can turn off geo-location data collection at any time by accessing the privacy settings of your mobile device. Depending on the device, you may also be able to reset its advertising identifier by accessing the privacy settings.

You also can engage with our content, such as video, applications, and other offerings, on or through third-party social networking sites, such as Facebook, and Talizma third-party social media plug-ins and applications. When you engage with our content on or through third party social networking sites, plug-ins or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, location, user files like photos and videos, your list of friends, people you follow and/or who follow you, the posts or the ‘likes’ you make, etc.) to deliver the content or as part of the operation of the application. We may also obtain non-personally identifiable information (e.g., content viewed, game performance, high scores, and information about advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on) from your interaction with our content. Through some social networking sites’ privacy settings, you can control what data you share. For more information about how social networking sites handle your personal information, please refer to their privacy policies and terms of use.

We, our service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, and partners may collect various types of non-personally identifiable information when you visit the Talizma Sites. The information may be collected via cookies, log files, and web beacons (aka “clear GIFs”).

Cookies are text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters that are placed in your computer’s browser. Cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. However, once you choose to furnish a Site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Talizma Sites may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.

Log files automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website (“Server Logs”). These Server Logs may include your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your visit, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

**How We Use the Information**

We will not share your personally identifiable information to third parties and will not share with any third party for sending marketing messages to you without your consent or as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for sending newsletters, partnered marketing promotions. We may use web beacons in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, services or customized experiences. If you register and create an account with a Site, the screen name you select as well as other content you submit to your profile (such as photos, comments, video content, or reviews) will be displayed publicly on the Site and may be reused and redistributed by us in our discretion.

We use information collected via cookies, clear gifs, and web beacons to: (a) store your preferences; (b) understand Site and Internet use; (c) improve Site design and content; (d) manage and measure the performance of advertisements displayed on or delivered by or through the Talizma Sites; (e) monitor the behavior of and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page; (f) customize the content, offerings, or advertisements you see on the Talizma Sites; and (g) offer you products, programs, or services.

**How We Share and Disclose the Information**

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Talizma Sites and applicable laws or as otherwise required or permitted by law or consistent with legal requirements.

Our agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this privacy notice and are not authorized to use the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us.

We may share non-personally identifiable information with third parties to help them to understand the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, or functionality on the Talizma Sites. We may also share non-personally identifiable information with third parties to provide users with additional or more relevant product and service opportunities.

**Analytics, Third Party Advertising, and Ad Choices**

We may use the services of reputable third parties to provide us with data collection, reporting, ad response measurement, and Site analytics, and to also assist us with delivery of relevant marketing messages and advertisements. These third parties may view, edit, or set their own cookies. The use of such technologies by these third parties is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by this privacy notice.

Advertising enables us to provide you with the content for which we are known. Our goal is to deliver advertising that is relevant to you. As part of this process we, our third party service providers, advertisers, advertising networks and platforms, agencies, or our partners may collect information about your online activities across the Talizma Sites and other sites, and supplement such information with information from third parties, in an effort to make inferences about your interests and deliver to you advertisements targeted to those interests.

At this time, the Talizma Sites do not recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include “do not track” instructions. However, you can change your privacy preferences regarding the use of cookies and similar technologies through your browser. Please consult the “Help” section of your browser for more information.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, to maintain data security, and to use correctly the information we collect online. However, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this privacy notice.

**Our Commitment To Childrens’ Privacy**

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of the Talizma Sites is directed to persons under 13. If you are under 13 years of age, then do not use or access the Talizma Sites at any time or in any manner. If we learn that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected on the Talizma Sites without verified parental consent, then we will take appropriate steps to delete this information.

Merger, Sale, or Bankruptcy

In the event that we are acquired by or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors’ rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

**Revisions and Effective Date**

From time to time, we may modify this privacy statement. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received the personal information you provided. For revisions that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information. Your continued use of the Talizma Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

This Privacy Notice was last revised on August 14th, 2014.

In case you have any questions or concerns, please mail us at: contact@Talizma.com
